Were you afraid, Punky?
你当时害怕吗, 小乖乖?
I was on the stage at the Roadhouse,
and the Iights went out.
我当时就站在路吧的舞台上,
所有灯光都熄灭了.
I kept thinking:
我当时不断的在想:
''The Iights are going out,
the Iights are going out.''
"灯就快灭了,
灯就快灭了."
And then they did.
然后它们呢真的都灭了.
And it aII went bIack,
and I kept thinking:
全场漆黑一片,
然后我又不断的想:
''It's so dark,
what about hand signaIs?
"这里这么黑,
打手势有用么?
What good wouId they do us now?
它们现在会对我们有帮助吗?
And the baby, what if the Iights
went out in the hospitaI
还想到宝宝, 如果医院里的
灯熄灭了怎么办
and we were in the eIevator?''
而我们刚好在电梯里?"
Then I'd heIp you have that baby
right there in the eIevator,
那我就在电梯里
当着上帝及众人的面,
in front of God and everybody.
帮你接生.
- I Iove you.
- 我爱你.
Coop, I've got deputies
from three counties Iooking for EarIe.
库, 我动用了3个镇的
警力去找厄尔.
He seems to have
compIeteIy disappeared.
但他似乎
完全失踪了.
Harry, the onIy hope we have
of finding them
哈里, 我们能
找到他们的唯一希望
is somewhere in this map.
就在这地图上的某处.
Giant, IittIe man,
巨人, 小人,
fire, fire waIk with me.
火, 火与我同行.
Fire waIk with me.
火与我同行.
Grand theft auto.
这个窃车大盗.
The Log Lady stoIe my truck.
圆木姑姑偷了我的火车.
'68 Dodge pickup.
68年原产道奇小货车.
Powder bIue.
浅灰蓝色.
I tried to chase after her,
but she took off
我试着去追她,
结果就在通往树林的那条路上
on the road up towards the woods.
给她甩了.
Pete, the Log Lady
did not steaI your truck.
皮特, 圆木姑姑
没有偷你的货车.
The Log Lady wiII be here
in one minute.
圆木姑姑会在一分钟内
出现在这里.
The woods, Harry,
树林, 哈里,
- Ghostwood forest.
- Ghostwood?
- 格斯伍森林.
- 格斯伍?
TweIve rainbow trouts in the bed.
12条虹鳟跃上河床，奇闻吧.
Wait a doggone minute.
12条? 等等，哎呀.
There's a circIe of 1 2 sycamores.
有一个由12棵小无花果树组成的圆圈.
GIastonbury Grove.
叫格顿伯利小树林.
Sycamores.
无花果树.
That's where I found the bIoody toweI
and the pages of the diary.
我就是在那里找到血毛巾
和日记散页的.
The Iegendary buriaI pIace
of King Arthur.
传说中
亚瑟王的埋葬地.
GIastonbury.
格顿伯利.
King Arthur's buried in EngIand.
可亚瑟王埋葬在英格兰啊.
WeII, Iast I heard anyway.
嗯, 反正我听说最后是的.
Right on time.
时间刚好.
It's the Log Lady.
是圆木姑姑.
Where's my truck?
我的货车在哪儿?
Pete, Windom EarIe stoIe your truck.
皮特, 是云顿·厄尔偷了你的车.
I brought the oiI.
我把油带来了.
Thank you, Margaret.
谢谢你, 玛格利特.
It sure Iooked to me Iike you.
在我看来他很像你.
Margaret,
玛格利特,
what did your husband
say exactIy about this oiI?
关于这油
你丈夫具体说过什么?
He brought it back one night
just before he died and said:
就在他临死前一晚
把它带回来，并说:
''This oiI is an opening to a gateway.''
"这油开启大门."
Intriguing, isn't it?
怪有趣的，是不是?
Jacoby.
杰柯比.
- Scorched engine oiI.
- 引擎焦油.
Hawk, bring in Ronette PuIaski.
豪克, 带朗尼特·珀拉斯奇进来.
Ronette, thanks for coming in.
朗尼特, 谢谢你来.
Do you recognize this smeII?
你认得出这味道吗?
Yes.
认得.
The night Laura PaImer was kiIIed.
就是劳拉·帕尔默被杀的那晚.
GIastonbury Grove.
格顿伯利小树林.
I am Windom EarIe.
我是云顿·厄尔.
Windom EarIe?
云顿·厄尔?
Take a Iook at that.
开这个.
TweIve rainbow trout.
12条虹鳟.
If you're gonna kiII me,
get it over with.
如果你要杀我,
就快点动手吧.
There's pIenty of time for that.
急什么，有大把时间.
But I do Iike the fear I'm feeIing.
而我喜欢这份恐惧感.
Our bones are scattered
at the grave's mouth,
每当有人对地球上
树木乱砍乱伐之际,
as when one cutteth
wood upon the earth.
我们的尸骨就会随之
零乱洒落在墓穴之口.
But mine eyes are unto thee,
O God the Lord:
但吾以眼乞求汝,
主耶和华:
in thee is my trust;
Ieave not my--
汝是吾之投靠;
切莫离弃吾--
Keep me from the snares
they have Iaid for me,
恶人已为我设下天罗地网，
还有那罪孽之人的邪恶圈套,
and the gins of the workers
of iniquity.
请带我远离这些
陷阱吧.
Let the wicked faII into their own nets,
whiIst that I withaI escape.
让那些恶人自食其果,
而我此时得以逃脱.
What are we doing here?
我们来这儿干嘛?
You and I have an appointment
at the end of the worId.
你和我有个
天涯之约.
- He'II come for me.
- No, he won't.
- 他会来找我的.
- 不, 他不会了.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- Same thing happened Iast time.
- 你为什么要这样对我?
- 因为上次发生过同样的事.
When he feII in Iove with my wife.
当他和我太太共坠爱河时.
I took the boy right to the edge
that time.
那次，我几乎把
那小子推向边缘了.
Come in, come in to the circIe!
进来, 进来圆圈这儿!
I teII you, they have not died.
我告诉你, 他们还没死.
Their hands cIasp, yours and mine.
他们的手紧握一起, 还有你和我的.
You'II not run from me now,
现在，你不会从我这逃跑了,
not in this circIe of trees.
在这圈树里，你不会跑.
You'II come with me.
你会跟着我.
Remember, 20 minutes on
and 20 minutes off with the ice bag.
记住, 用这冰袋敷20十分钟
然后拿开，休息20分钟.
It'II heIp with the sweIIing,
both of you.
这对治疗你们俩的肿伤,
都有帮助.
Take some aspirin,
caII me in the morning.
吃点阿斯匹林,
早上给我电话.
Thanks, doc.
谢谢了, 医生.
Does it hurt much, baby?
伤的很厉害吗, 宝贝?
God, Nadine,
I was so worried about you.
上帝, 纳丁,
我刚才好担心你啊.
I admit there were times
when I had my doubts
我承认我有时
也会怀疑
about what we meant to each other,
but seeing that sandbag hit you,
我们彼此之间到底意味着什么,
但看着那个沙袋砸到你那一刻,
I just knew
我就知道
I'd practicaIIy do anything for you.
我简直愿意为你做任何事
And then the tree hit me.
之后那棵树就砸到我了.
I Iove you.
我爱你.
There, I've said it and I'm gIad.
好了, 我很高兴我说出来了.
Who are you?
你是谁?
Mike.
迈克.
You--
你--
You try to--
You say your name is Mike?
你竟想--
你说你叫迈克?
What are you doing in my house?
你在我家里干什么?
You brought me here, Nadine.
你带我来这儿的, 纳丁.
No!
不!
No, you get out of here!
不可能, 你快滚出这里!
Ed, make him go away.
艾德, 快把他赶出去.
What's she doing here?
她在这儿又是做什么?
It's not fair.
这不公平.
PIease...
求你了...
Ed, make...
艾德, 赶他...
Where are my drape runners?
我的滑轨窗帘去哪儿了?
Nadine, how oId are you?
纳丁, 你多大了?
What kind of a stupid question
is that?
这是什么
蠢问题?
Answer me. How oId are you?
回答我. 你几岁了?
Thirty-five, you moron!
35, 你白痴啊!
I'm sorry, Ed.
真对不起, 艾德.
I think I Iet things
get a IittIe out of hand.
我想是我
把事情搞糟了.
Oh, no. No.
噢, 不要. 不要.
Donna, pIease.
Donna, pIease Iisten.
唐娜, 求你了.
唐娜, 请听我说.
- I've heard enough.
- PIease, just Iet me expIain.
- 我已经听够了.
- 求你了, 让我解释.
- Donna...
- Leave me aIone!
- 唐娜...
- 别烦我!
It isn't your parents' fauIt. It's mine.
这不是你父母的错. 都是我害的.
My parents?
Who are my parents anyway?
我父母?
我父母到底是谁啊?
I onIy wanted to do good.
I wanted to be good.
我只不过想做好事.
想做个好人.
And it feIt so good to teII the truth
时隔多年，终于说出了真相
after aII these years.
这感觉真好.
Ben, damn it.
本, 你真该死.
- WiII.
- Donna.
- 伟.
- 唐娜.
Ben, I warned you.
Get out of my house.
本, 我警告你.
滚出我的房子.
WiII,
伟,
can you forgive me
for what I have done to you?
你能原谅
我所对你做过的事吗?
SyIvia, I toId you to stay home.
你到底想对着家人干什么呀?
What are you trying to do
to this famiIy?
爸爸，你是我爸爸
你才是我爸爸?
Daddy, you're my daddy.
You're my daddy.
你才是我爸爸.
爸爸.
Daddy.
Leave my famiIy aIone!
别来搞我家人!
Now, WiII. WiII!
那, 伟. 伟!
WiII!
伟!
No!
不!
I knew I'd seen it somewhere.
我就知道在哪儿见过它.
Safety deposit box.
保险柜.
They'II never notice the difference.
他们不会注意到区别的.
Oh, Andrew.
噢, 安德鲁.
Good night, Pete.
晚安, 皮特.
Harry,
哈利,
this way.
这边.
Coop?
库?
Harry, I have to go on aIone.
哈里, 我得独自去.
Why?
为什么?
What?
什么?
Sycamore trees.
小无花果树.
An opening to a gateway.
一个开放的大门.
Footprints.
脚印.
My God.
我的上帝.
Under the sycamore tree
无花果树之下
And I'II see you
我你将
And you'II see me
相会
And I'II see you in the branches
我看见你随树枝
That bIow in the breeze
迎风飘飞
I'II see you in the trees
我将和你在那树相会
Under the sycamore tree
在无花果树下
Sheriff Truman?
杜鲁门警长?
Andy! Over here!
安迪! 过来这里!
Been about ten hours
since he went in there.
他进去那里
差不多已经10小时了.
Do you want a thermos of coffee?
你要来一瓶暖咖啡?
Yeah.
好.
Do you want a pIate speciaI?
你要来一碟特色菜?
Yeah.
好.
Do you want dessert?
你要甜点?
Yeah.
好.
Do you want pie?
你要馅饼?
Harry?
哈里?
- Morning, Mr. MibbIer.
- Audrey Horne.
- 早, 米不乐先生.
- 欧蕊·荷恩.
This is my fortunate day.
今天可是我的幸运日.
Is there anything I can do for you?
有什么我可以为你效劳的?
As a matter of fact, there is.
You can caII the Twin Peaks Gazette.
还真有事要你做.
你可以致电双峰报.
Ask to speak
with Dwayne MiIford Jr.
要求找
小杜恩·妙福谈.
- Dwayne?
- The editor.
- 杜恩?
- 那个编辑.
We must make a teIephone caII.
我们必须打电话吗.
- Yes?
- Yes.
- 肯定?
- 是.
TeII him that Audrey Horne
has chained herseIf
告诉他欧蕊·荷恩
已经用锁链
to the Twin Peaks
Savings and Loan vauIt
把她自己锁在
双峰镇的储贷保险库了
in protest of their financiaI ties
来抗议他们和格斯伍
to the Ghostwood
DeveIopment Project.
发展项目之间
的金融瓜葛.
And that I intend to stay here
untiI a town meeting is heId
我打算留在这里
直到镇上举行会议
to debate the future
of our environment
讨论我们将来的
环境问题
and specificaIIy the effect
of the Ghostwood Project upon it.
特别是格斯伍项目
在这上面的影响.
- Okay?
- Yeah, miss.
- 知道了吗?
- 知道了, 小姐.
And can I get a gIass of water,
pIease?
那我可以要杯水吗,
麻烦了?
Thank you, DeII.
谢谢你, 带尔.
You, you.
你, 你.
You!
你!
DeII MibbIer, as I Iive and breathe.
带尔·米不乐, 我依然健在啊.
He's aIive.
他还活着.
But the funeraI.
但那个葬礼.
And aII of the fIowers,
and the choir boys.
还有那些花,
和唱诗童.
I was hoping you couId do
a smaII favor for me.
我希望你能
帮我一个小忙.
Does this Iook famiIiar to you?
你觉得看来眼熟吗?
Yes, it's one
of our safety deposit keys.
眼熟, 是我们其中一个
保险柜的钥匙.
- ShaII we?
- WeII, of course.
- 我们可以去打开吗?
- 这, 当然可以.
But there is going to be
a bit of a probIem.
但马上就会有
一点点小麻烦.
A bit of a probIem.
一点小问题.
- Hi, Pete.
- Audrey?
- 嗨, 皮特.
- 欧蕊?
Young Iady, why are you
chained to the bank vauIt?
小姑娘, 你为什么
拴在银库这儿?
CiviI disobedience.
这叫非暴力抵抗.
Waste no time arguing
what a good man shouId be, be one.
不浪费时间做无谓的争论
你肯定是一个, 有志气的人.
Marcus AureIius.
I admire your verve.
就像教皇兼大哲学家马可·奥里略.
我钦佩你的气魄.
I see no probIem here.
If you'II excuse us, pIease?
我没看到这里有任何问题.
如果你不介意我们进去, 好吗?
Sure.
当然.
Did you caII the Gazette yet?
你打电话给报社 没?
Maybe you shouId caII the sheriff too.
Ask for Agent Cooper.
或许你还该打电话去警察局.
找库珀探员.
Give me the key.
给我钥匙.
A boy? It's a boy!
一个男孩? 是一个男孩!
It's a boy, it's a boy.
是个男孩, 是个男孩.
- So Iong.
- 再会.
We've come to the end
of a Iong road, Pete.
我们终于来到
漫漫长路的尽头了, 皮特.
And here we are.
那我们来吧.
Oh, sh--!
噢, 妈的--!
SheIIy, I think we shouId get married.
雪莉, 我想我们该结婚了.
Bobby.
波比.
Leo. I'm stiII wearing his ring.
里欧. 我还戴着他的戒指呢.
Oh, what kept us, Heidi?
噢, 怎么回来晚了, 海蒂?
Seconds on knackwurst
this morning?
因为今早又要吃
第二次德国蒜肠吗?
I couIdn't get my car started.
我的车打不着火了.
Too busy jump-starting the oId man.
我看你是忙着为家里那个老家伙打火吧.
- Again.
- 又来了.
I thought you Germans
were aIways on time.
我还以为你们德国人
永远都准时呢.
- SheIIy...
- Bobby.
- 雪莉...
- 波比.
Leo's probabIy up in the woods
having the time of his Iife.
搞不好，现在里欧正在树林里
享受他的人生呢.
WeII, you were right,
there's the major.
啊, 你是对的,
少校在那儿呢.
Excuse us, Major Briggs,
for the intrusion,
布里格斯少校,
抱歉我们打搅了,
but Sarah here had a message for you
that she thought was important.
但莎拉觉得她这儿
有很重要的消息要给你.
Sarah.
莎拉.
I'm in the BIack Lodge
with DaIe Cooper.
我正和戴尔·库珀
在守夜门.
I'm waiting for you.
我正等着你呢.
当你再次到见我
我将不再是我自己
这是接待室
你要来杯咖啡吗？
你的一些朋友都在这儿呢
你好，库珀探员
25年后，我会再次见到你
哈利路亚！
咖啡，咖啡，咖啡...
还有一个一样的
哇，鲍勃，哇！
火，与我同行
走错了
另一个朋友来了
我是马蒂,小心我表姐
另一个自己
同时...
凯若琳.
CaroIine.
安妮.
Annie.
安妮!
Annie!
安妮. 安妮.
Annie. Annie.
安妮?
Annie?
戴尔，我看见杀我那个人的脸了
安妮,
Annie,
杀你那个人的脸?
the face of the man who kiIIed you?
就是我丈夫
安妮?
Annie?
谁是安妮？
是我。
凯若琳.
CaroIine.
你肯定是又搞错了。
我还活着。
戴尔·库珀
如果你把灵魂交给我
我就让安妮活命。
我愿意
I wiII.
你走
这错了。
他不能向你要灵魂
我要带走他的灵魂
我没有杀人
库珀!
Cooper!
安妮!
Annie!
安妮.
Annie.
安妮!
Annie!
他醒了.
There he is.
库?
Coop?
我没睡.
I wasn't sIeeping.
安妮, 安妮怎样了?
Annie, how's Annie?
她一定会好的.
She's gonna be just fine.
她在医院那边.
She's over at the hospitaI.
我要刷牙.
I need to brush my teeth.
好的. 来.
Sure. Come on.
我扶你起来.
I'II heIp you up.
现在慢点来.
Take her easy now.
我要刷牙了.
I need to brush my teeth.
好主意.
Good idea.
库?
Coop?
库, 你还好吧?
Coop, are you okay?
库?
Coop?
安妮怎样了? 安妮怎样了?
How is Annie? How's Annie?
安妮怎样了?
How's Annie?
安妮怎样了? 安妮怎样了?
How's Annie? How's Annie?
安妮怎样了?
How's Annie?